http://www.kaon.com/privacy

OVERVIEW
Kaon AR® (AUGMENTED REALITY)
Kaon VR® (VIRTUAL REALITY)
OVERVIEW
Kaon AR® (AUGMENTED REALITY)
Kaon VR® (VIRTUAL REALITY)
About Us
Why Kaon?
Why Interactivity?
Privacy statement for kaon.com
Kaon Interactive is Committed to Protecting Your PrivacyWe understand that the information we collect about you is your information, and we intend to keep it that way.1. General Information and DisclaimerThe use of the websites of Kaon Interactive Inc. (www.kaon.com) (hereinafter referred to as the “Websites”), offered by Kaon Interactive Inc., implies in all cases the collection of certain information about its customers and service users.This Privacy Policy is applicable to all customers, users, data subjects and/or other persons who contact Kaon Interactive for any reason and who access the Websites (hereinafter referred to as the ”Web Users”).This Privacy Policy contains a detailed description of the following: (i) the data collected about Kaon Interactive Web Users and their employees, (ii) the purpose of processing such information and (iii) how the use of such information can be governed and controlled by Kaon Interactive.This Privacy Policy is applicable to all services offered on the Websites, along with any pages or services that could be added to the Websites in the future, and it is subject to the terms and conditions set out in the applicable regulations on data protection and on information society services and electronic commerce.This privacy policy update meets the obligations of EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).2. ControllerUnless stated otherwise, Kaon Interactive is the controller of the personal data collected by means of these Websites.For any query, request or clarification regarding the processing of your personal data, you may contact the email and post addresses provided as follows: Kaon Interactive Inc., 3 Mill & Main Place, Suite 200, Maynard, MA 01754, USA; or webmaster@kaon.com3. The Personal Data Subject to ProcessingFor the purpose of rendering the services offered, Kaon Interactive will process the following personal data:Any initial data you voluntarily provide to us in your application to be registered as a user of the Websites, your request for information from our company, your request to subscribe to our newsletters or your request to obtain the services offered by Kaon Interactive. In each form, we will clearly and precisely specify which data you must provide on a mandatory basis to proceed with the application, request or service request you submit to us from time to time.Any data that are generated or exchanged with you after your initial application in order to fulfill such initial application.Any data generated in relation with the use of the Websites by using cookies and information from the log file, including the IP address, the kind of browser, the URLs, the number of clicks and the way in which the User interacts with links, domain names, landing pages and pages visited. By continuing to use this site you are giving us your consent to do this.The Web Users guarantee the authenticity and truthfulness of all data provided through the Websites and must update any information provided to Kaon Interactive so that it matches the real and current situation at all times. The Web Users shall be held liable for any false or inaccurate statement and any damages this may cause to Kaon Interactive or any third parties.Kaon Interactive shall manage the data collected pursuant to applicable laws and in accordance with the terms and conditions set out in this Privacy Policy.4. Use of Personal DataThe personal data provided to Kaon Interactive will be used to process and manage requests made by the Web Users to Kaon Interactive at any time, regardless of whether these are for information, registration or obtaining the services offered by the company. Kaon Interactive may also use personal data for the following purposes:Managing and controlling the Web Users’ transactions and offering services to them through the Websites, email, eNewsletters, telephone, and other means of communication, managing and controlling compliance by the Web Users with the terms and conditions of our Websites and their accounts, managing and controlling their user account on the Websites, sending, including by electronic means, promotional information about the products and services offered by Kaon Interactive similar to those included in the requests received from its customers and/or Web Users only where you EXPRESSLY CONSENT to this. You can stop receiving promotional emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in every email sent.5. Authorization for the data ProcessingKaon Interactive is authorized to process your data for the purpose of managing and processing requests by Web Users as this is necessary for Kaon Interactive to fulfill its contractual or other obligations in relation with such requests.Regarding the dispatch of promotional information about products and services similar in nature to those requested or purchased by the Web Users, such processing is in the legitimate interest of Kaon Interactive, which is expressly acknowledged by the data protection regulations and is expressly authorized in the regulations on information society services. Web Users may, now or at any other time, object to receiving commercial notices about Kaon Interactive’s products and services by sending an email message to webmaster@kaon.com.Your continued use of Kaon Interactive’s service will be considered acceptance of our updated terms.6. Data Disclosures, International Transfers and Automated Decision-MakingKaon Interactive does not disclose data to third parties without first obtaining your consent, except where necessary to fulfill the legal and contractual obligations to which Kaon Interactive is subject at any time due to its nature and business.In this respect, Kaon Interactive hereby informs you that your data may be disclosed to service providers with whom Kaon Interactive has signed the relevant agreements pursuant to the applicable regulations.Kaon Interactive uses services rendered by technology providers located in countries that do not have regulations equivalent to the European regulations. Its use of these services meets all the requirements set by the data protection regulations, with the guarantees and safeguards required to protect your privacy being applied to transfers of your data.For more information about how your privacy is guaranteed, you may contact the Data Protection Officer through the specified post and email addresses.Kaon Interactive does not adopt any decisions that could affect you in a significant manner based solely on automated processing of your data. All decision-making processes of our company related to your requests, services, queries or purchases are conducted with the involvement of a human being.7. Security and Confidentiality Measures Applied to the DataKaon Interactive has implemented and maintains administrative, technical and organizational measures appropriate to the kind of data it collects and subject to the terms and conditions set out in the applicable data protection regulations for the purpose of protecting the personal information provided to Kaon Interactive against unauthorized or unlawful access and accidental loss, damage, alteration or destruction of data. Only authorized staff may access the personal information and they may only do so for the permitted business purposes. Notwithstanding the foregoing, criminal acts may be committed by third parties even where Kaon Interactive uses all the means at its disposal to prevent such acts.Despite this, the user is responsible for suitably protecting any codes and passwords provided for access and prevent them from being used or accessed by unauthorized third parties. Kaon Interactive cannot be held liable for any inappropriate use of the user name and password carried out by any user.8. Privacy Shield (relevant to our EU customers) We store European customer information on our servers located in the United States. We comply with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States, respectively. We have certified to the Department of Commerce that we adhere to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in our privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/.Under the Privacy Shield Framework, we are subject to the authority of the Federal Trade Commission. If you have any questions or concerns relating to our Privacy Shield certification, contact us via email at webmaster@kaon.com. If we are not able to resolve your concern, you may also contact your European Data Protection Authority or Commission or seek assistance from our designated Privacy Shield independent recourse mechanism, JAMS, at https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield. In certain circumstances, you may also have the right to pursue binding arbitration through the Privacy Shield Framework, as described in Annex I to the Privacy Shield Principles.a.) If we have received your personal information under the Privacy Shield and subsequently transfer it to a third party service provider for processing as described in this privacy policy, we will remain responsible if these providers process your personal information in a manner inconsistent with the Privacy Shield Principles, except where we can establish that we were not responsible for the violation.b.) To respond to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.c.) To transfer your information in connection with a sale, merger, consolidation, liquidation, reorganization, acquisition, or related negotiation. If we decide to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganize our business, this may involve us disclosing your information to prospective or actual purchasers and their advisers. If such transactions are consummated, they may include, but not be limited to, the sale or transfer of all or substantially all of our assets, including, but not limited to, our email distribution list and your personally identifiable information.d.) Finally, we may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party service providers. These statistics will not include any personally identifiable information.9. Exercising Your RightsYou may exercise your rights to withdraw any consent you granted, to access, rectification, erasure, portability, restriction and/or objection to the processing of your personal data at any time and free of charge by emailing webmaster@kaon.com.Kaon Interactive may review this Privacy Policy at any time. The current Privacy Policy will be available on the Websites at all times. Any updates thereto shall come into force immediately upon being published, which will be notified to all Web Users.10. AcceptanceBy providing their personal data to Kaon Interactive and/or by registering as a user and/or using the Websites, the Web Users expressly accept that their personal data will be used for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, which include, inter alia, commercial notices and storage of their personal data.Date of validity: May 25, 2018
Connect with us!
Copyright © Kaon Interactive, Inc. All rights reserved.
